Who did you get into a fight with this time?
مع من دخلت في شجار هذه المرة؟
How many times have I told you?
كم مرة أخبرتك بذلك؟
You are supposed to get along with your classmates.
من المفترض أن تكون علاقتك جيدة مع زملائك في الفصل.
You are an adult now.
أنت الآن شخص بالغ.
Can you take better care of your body?
هل يمكنك الاعتناء بجسمك بشكل أفضل؟
One hospital visit costs hundreds.
تكلفة زيارة واحدة للمستشفى مئات الدولارات.
Noisy.
صاخب.
You're driving me crazy.
أنت تُجنّنني.
This was the only thing,
كان هذا هو الشيء الوحيد،
the very last thing,
آخر شيء على الإطلاق،
I ever said to them
قلت لهم ذلك من قبل
before what had happened to them.
قبل ما حدث لهم.
Then you must really regret
إذن لا بد أنك تندم حقاً
not saying a proper goodbye to them.
لم أودعهم وداعاً لائقاً.
Regret?
يندم؟
I used to.
كنت أفعل ذلك.
But not anymore.
لكن ليس بعد الآن.
Because of you,
بفضلك،
that night
في تلك الليلة
became something different.
أصبح شيئاً مختلفاً.
You could even call it
بل يمكنك حتى تسميتها
a happy ending.
نهاية سعيدة.
So, there is nothing left to regret.
إذن، لم يعد هناك ما يدعو للندم.
You can talk about "regret" and "happiness" now.
يمكنك التحدث عن "الندم" و"السعادة" الآن.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
can I ask
هل لي أن أسأل؟
what happened to your mom afterward?
ماذا حدث لأمك بعد ذلك؟
My mom never woke up.
لم تستيقظ أمي أبداً.
As for my dad,
أما بالنسبة لأبي،
he was prosecuted for conducting illegal experiments.
تمت محاكمته بتهمة إجراء تجارب غير قانونية.
He set a car on fire
أشعل النار في سيارة
and left this world with my mom.
ورحلت عن هذه الدنيا مع أمي.
So after my brother graduated from college,
بعد تخرج أخي من الجامعة،
he went to work for the Special Administration Bureau.
ذهب للعمل في مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
He believes Ren are people
هو يعتقد أن رين هم بشر
who are deeply obsessive without normal emotions
الأشخاص الذين يعانون من هوس شديد دون مشاعر طبيعية
and must be strictly controlled.
ويجب التحكم بها بشكل صارم.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
You did not say anything about yourself.
لم تذكر شيئاً عن نفسك.
Your arms were covered in needle marks from your dad.
كانت ذراعيك مغطاة بآثار إبر من والدك.
Do you not resent him?
ألا تشعر بالاستياء تجاهه؟
I would be lying if I said I did not.
سأكون كاذباً لو قلت إنني لم أفعل.
Sometimes, I felt sad
أحياناً، كنت أشعر بالحزن
and wondered
وتساءل
if my father even loved me
إن كان والدي يحبني أصلاً
until I found
إلى أن وجدت
the real cause behind all that pain.
السبب الحقيقي وراء كل هذا الألم.
It was the Affinity virus.
كان ذلك فيروس أفينيتي.
My dad's obsession
هوس والدي
was actually caused by the Affinity B virus.
في الواقع، كان السبب هو فيروس Affinity B.
That is why I majored in biological sciences in college.
لهذا السبب تخصصت في العلوم البيولوجية في الجامعة.
Instead of tearing myself apart,
بدلاً من أن أمزق نفسي إرباً،
I might as well spend my time
من الأفضل أن أقضي وقتي
trying to crack this virus.
محاولة لفك شفرة هذا الفيروس.
Simply put, choose to love.
ببساطة، اختر أن تحب.
Choose to change things.
اختر أن تغير الأمور.
It is much happier and easier than hating.
إنها أسعد وأسهل بكثير من الكراهية.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I prepared a small gift for you today.
لقد أعددت لك هدية صغيرة اليوم.
I might have dropped it on the way.
ربما أسقطته في الطريق.
I will go look for it.
سأذهب للبحث عنه.
Wait here. I will be right back.
انتظر هنا. سأعود حالاً.
Hello, sir.
أهلاً سيدي.
Are you still taking the medication I gave you before?
هل ما زلت تتناول الدواء الذي وصفته لك من قبل؟
Yes.
نعم.
And it works much better than I expected.
وهو يعمل بشكل أفضل بكثير مما توقعت.
I am experiencing feelings I never had before.
أشعر بمشاعر لم أشعر بها من قبل.
Mr. Ding?
السيد دينغ؟
I was going to tell you
كنت سأخبرك
that I grabbed the wrong thing when I made the prescription.
أنني أخذت الشيء الخطأ عندما كتبت الوصفة الطبية.
What I gave you
ما أعطيتك
was just vitamins.
كانت مجرد فيتامينات.
But if you are certain you are having new emotional experiences,
لكن إذا كنت متأكدًا من أنك تمر بتجارب عاطفية جديدة،
the only explanation is that you suddenly gained
التفسير الوحيد هو أنك اكتسبت فجأة
normal emotional perception.
الإدراك العاطفي الطبيعي.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Are these
هل هذه
my tears?
دموعي؟
I had only ever seen them
لم أرهم من قبل إلا هم
on people I thought were soft.
عن أشخاص كنت أظنهم ضعفاء.
I once believed they were a sign of weakness.
كنت أعتقد في السابق أنها علامة ضعف.
Until she appeared.
إلى أن ظهرت.
I started to envy her tears
بدأت أشعر بالغيرة من دموعها
and her wholeness.
وكمالها.
Maybe when her virus entered my body,
ربما عندما دخل فيروسها إلى جسدي،
it brought that wholeness with it.
لقد جلبت معها ذلك الكمال.
Then what could be called a miracle of happiness
ثم ما يمكن تسميته بمعجزة السعادة
happened.
حدث ذلك.
For someone who can love,
لشخص قادر على الحب،
when facing the one they love,
عند مواجهة من يحبون،
what is the instinctive reaction?
ما هو رد الفعل الغريزي؟
Found it.
وجدته.
Luckily, I did not lose it.
لحسن الحظ، لم أفقدها.
I spent a long time drawing it with AI.
لقد أمضيت وقتاً طويلاً في رسمها باستخدام الذكاء الاصطناعي.
Be good.
كن طيباً.
Go take a hot shower.
اذهب واستحم بماء ساخن.
So I made the first move just now?
هل قمت بالخطوة الأولى الآن؟
This is such a mess.
هذا فوضى عارمة.
I actually fell for someone with emotional deficiency.
لقد وقعت في حب شخص يعاني من قصور عاطفي.
But he really acts as if he likes me.
لكنه يتصرف فعلاً وكأنه معجب بي.
Maybe his condition got better.
ربما تحسنت حالته.
By adjusting neurotransmitters in the brain,
عن طريق تعديل النواقل العصبية في الدماغ،
[Emotion Emotional Supplement]
[مكمل عاطفي]
emotional states can be simulated.
يمكن محاكاة الحالات العاطفية.
Is he taking medicine that simulates emotions?
هل يتناول دواءً يحاكي المشاعر؟
All the care and affection he's shown me during this time,
كل الرعاية والمودة التي أظهرها لي خلال هذه الفترة،
was it all just because of the medicine?
هل كان السبب في كل ذلك هو الدواء؟
Did he take it to trick my feelings
هل أخذها ليخدع مشاعري؟
so I would willingly form a pact?
إذن، هل سأعقد اتفاقاً عن طيب خاطر؟
If that is really the case,
إذا كان هذا هو الحال فعلاً،
I will cut things off completely.
سأقطع كل شيء تماماً.
My medication.
أدويتي.
Why can't I move?
لماذا لا أستطيع التحرك؟
Do you feel weak all over?
هل تشعر بالضعف في جميع أنحاء جسمك؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You're not sick.
أنت لست مريضاً.
I just took advantage of you while you were asleep
لقد استغليتك وأنت نائم
and slipped you a few pills.
وأعطاك بعض الحبوب.
They won't seriously harm you.
لن يلحقوا بك ضرراً بالغاً.
They're just
إنهم فقط
to make sure you don't have the strength to run.
للتأكد من أنك لا تملك القوة الكافية للركض.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
You can't distance yourself from me
لا يمكنك الابتعاد عني
or abandon me.
أو أن يتخلوا عني.
You must be hungry.
لا بد أنك جائع.
Let's go get breakfast.
هيا بنا نتناول الفطور.
After breakfast,
بعد الإفطار،
I'll give you a few more pills.
سأعطيك بضع حبات أخرى.
No.
لا.
So it was just a dream.
إذن كان مجرد حلم.
[Xie Xinxu]
[شيه شينكسو]
Get up.
استيقظ.
Breakfast.
إفطار.
Go sit across from me.
اجلس قبالتي.
I found this in your jacket pocket yesterday.
وجدت هذا في جيب سترتك أمس.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Medicine?
الدواء؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
Just regular vitamins.
مجرد فيتامينات عادية.
So when did you start taking them?
متى بدأت بتناولها؟
After the wedding.
بعد الزفاف.
I don't want anything too greasy this early.
لا أريد أي شيء دهني جداً في هذه المرحلة المبكرة.
Mr. Ding says he has news about the second fragment.
يقول السيد دينغ إنه لديه أخبار بشأن الجزء الثاني.
That fragment was bought at an underground auction half a year ago.
تم شراء تلك القطعة في مزاد تحت الأرض قبل ستة أشهر.
By an anonymous collector
بواسطة جامع مجهول
from a neighboring city.
من مدينة مجاورة.
But
لكن
their real identity is unknown.
هويتهم الحقيقية غير معروفة.
It won't be easy to track down.
لن يكون من السهل العثور عليه.
I have a way.
لديّ طريقة.
Collectors like that
يحب هواة الجمع ذلك
usually insure their collections.
عادة ما يؤمّنون على مجموعاتهم.
[Liu Huanian, Account Manager at Ning'an Insurance]
[ليو هوانيان، مدير حسابات في شركة نينغان للتأمين]
Thank you both for trusting our company.
شكراً لكما على ثقتكما بشركتنا.
Manager Liu, can this be insured?
يا سيد ليو، هل يمكن التأمين على هذا؟
How much coverage can it get?
ما مدى التغطية الإعلامية التي يمكن أن يحظى بها؟
Three million.
ثلاثة ملايين.
That much coverage?
كل هذه التغطية؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Previously, a famous collector
في السابق، جامع تحف مشهور
named Yin Che
يُدعى يين تشي
came to our company
جاء إلى شركتنا
with something
مع شيء ما
very similar to yours,
يشبه كثيراً ما لديك،
and he insured it for three million.
وقام بتأمينها بمبلغ ثلاثة ملايين.
A collector named Yin Che.
جامع تحف يُدعى ين تشي.
I've danced over a dozen times. That's enough.
لقد رقصت أكثر من اثنتي عشرة مرة. هذا يكفي.
Let post-production handle it.
دع مرحلة ما بعد الإنتاج تتولى الأمر.
Yes, Director Xia.
نعم، أيها المخرج شيا.
Shooting this stuff every day is driving me crazy.
تصوير هذه الأشياء كل يوم يُجنّنني.
PR really knows how to come up with ways to torture me.
قسم العلاقات العامة يعرف حقاً كيف يبتكر طرقاً لتعذيبي.
You're the head of the Special Administration Bureau, after all.
أنت رئيس مكتب الإدارة الخاصة، في نهاية المطاف.
There's no harm done
لم يحدث أي ضرر
in building a friendly public image.
في بناء صورة عامة ودية.
Back to business.
لنعد إلى العمل.
Remember that glass disk I mentioned
أتذكر ذلك القرص الزجاجي الذي ذكرته؟
that contains information
التي تحتوي على معلومات
on the Affinity treatment?
بخصوص علاج أفينيتي؟
There's news.
هناك أخبار.
What do you need me to do?
ماذا تريدني أن أفعل؟
One of the disk fragments
أحد أجزاء القرص
is in the hands of a collector named Yin Che.
وهي الآن في حوزة جامع تحف يُدعى ين تشي.
Find a way to get it.
ابحث عن طريقة للحصول عليه.
This drug must never be allowed to see the light of day.
يجب ألا يُسمح لهذا الدواء بالظهور في الأسواق أبداً.
Remember.
يتذكر.
This drug must never be allowed to come out, ever.
يجب ألا يُسمح لهذا الدواء بالظهور أبداً.
Sorry, we're not sharing a table.
معذرةً، لن نتشارك طاولة واحدة.
Are you Yin Che?
هل أنت يين تشي؟
You bought a glass fragment
لقد اشتريت قطعة زجاج
at an underground auction the other day.
في مزاد سري في اليوم الآخر.
Would you be willing to sell it to us?
هل ترغب في بيعه لنا؟
We can match the price, or go higher.
بإمكاننا مطابقة السعر، أو حتى رفعه.
You managed to trace it back to me.
لقد تمكنت من تتبع الأمر إليّ.
You're not ordinary.
أنت لست شخصًا عاديًا.
I can give you the fragment for free.
يمكنني أن أعطيك الجزء مجاناً.
But
لكن
you'll have to do me a favor.
سيتعين عليك أن تسدي لي معروفاً.
This
هذا
is my friend's wife.
هي زوجة صديقي.
Her name is Qi.
اسمها تشي.
She's very beautiful.
إنها جميلة جداً.
The two of them
الاثنان
started living apart
بدأوا يعيشون منفصلين
a few months ago.
قبل بضعة أشهر.
Later, my friend noticed
وفي وقت لاحق، لاحظ صديقي ذلك
that her recent photos
صورها الأخيرة
[Qi's post] didn't look like selfies.
لم تكن منشورات [تشي] تبدو كصور سيلفي.
So my friend
إذن يا صديقي
suspects she's having an affair.
يشتبه في أنها على علاقة غرامية.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪